{
    "id": "b72eb2c9370c4e27b433c555dac6815d",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Every nation has …………………. traditions.",
            "description": "It's means it is or it has.",
            "answers": [
                "its",
                "it's"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time you ……………………. those carpets.",
            "description": "After it’s time, a past tense is used with a present meaning.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "washed",
                "wash",
                "have washed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. the bag on the table.",
            "description": "Laid is the past tense of lay to lay is to put something down flat.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "laid",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns ……………………. money than I do.",
            "description": "Use less with uncountable nouns.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His essay was chosen because it had the ……………………. mistakes.",
            "description": "Use fewest with plural nouns and least with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "least",
                "fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You look …………………… What happened?",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb we use adjectives, not adverbs to modify copular verbs.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "sad",
                "sadly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t make him ……………………. to me.",
            "description": "Make is followed by object + infinitive without to.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "to listen",
                "listen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I had to shout to make ……………………….. heard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She might not ……………………… to come with us.",
            "description": "Might is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "to want",
                "want",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She got married ……………………. her college sweetheart.",
            "description": "We use to after get married. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… our party will win the election.",
            "description": "Maybe is similar to perhaps.",
            "answers": [
                "Maybe",
                "May be",
                "Perhaps"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind people …………………….. you what to do?",
            "description": "We use ing forms or if-clauses after do you mind…? And would you mind….?\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "telling",
                "tell",
                "to tell"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}